Popup calculator Copy a link to this page Print this page Email a link to this page Scroll up to form What does this mean? Remove this row Open/Close content Close content Return to content Copy to clipboard

Quick Search: 

    Finance Calculators

    Pay

    Height / Length

    Mass (Weight)

    Volume

    Volume to Weight

    Force

    Area

    Area to Volume

    Energy

    Unit Converters

    Home / Garden

    Misc

    Time

    Math

    Cooking Calculators

    Health Calculators

**You are here:** [the calculator site](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/) » [privacy policy](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/privacypolicy.php) - information

Ezoic Services
==============

This website has an exclusive advertising contract with Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), a renowned leader in website optimization, enhancing user experiences, optimizing ad performance, and generating revenue through advanced AI-powered technology.  
Ezoic Services  
This website uses the services of Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), including to manage third-party interest-based advertising. Ezoic may employ a variety of technologies on this website, including tools to serve content, display advertisements and enable advertising to visitors of this website, which may utilize first and third-party cookies.  
A cookie is a small text file sent to your device by a web server that enables the website to remember information about your browsing activity. First-party cookies are created by the site you are visiting, while third-party cookies are set by domains other than the one you're visiting. Ezoic and our partners may place third-party cookies, tags, beacons, pixels, and similar technologies to monitor interactions with advertisements and optimize ad targeting. Please note that disabling cookies may limit access to certain content and features on the website, and rejecting cookies does not eliminate advertisements but will result in non-personalized advertising. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them [here](https://allaboutcookies.org/). The following information may be collected, used, and stored in a cookie when serving personalized ads:  

* IP address
* Operating system type and version
* Device type
* Language preferences
* Web browser type
* Email (in a hashed or encrypted form)

Ezoic and its partners may use this data in combination with information that has been independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements across various platforms and websites. Ezoic’s partners may also gather additional data, such as unique IDs, advertising IDs, geolocation data, usage data, device information, traffic data, referral sources, and interactions between users and websites or advertisements, to create audience segments for targeted advertising across different devices, browsers, and apps. You can find more information about interest-based advertising and how to manage them [here](https://youradchoices.com/).  
You can view Ezoic’s privacy policy [here](https://ezoic.com/privacy/), or for additional information about Ezoic’s advertising and other partners, you can view Ezoic’s advertising partners [here.](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/)

============================================================================

[The Calculator Site respects the confidentiality of the information relating to its individual users and visitors and the laws governing the privacy of information that apply in the country and state where the web site is located. Information identifying a user will not be disclosed by The Calculator Site staff to anyone unless specifically authorized by that individual.

To help with your productivity, The Calculator Site may place the following cookies (🍪) in your browser:

* **currency**: This cookie stores your chosen currency on finance calculators, in order to remember it and auto-select it for you on calculators during future visits.
* **conversion cookie**: For each of the main unit category converters, a cookie is placed to store the index of the last options chosen for 'Convert From' and 'Convert To'. This is to auto-select them for your future visits (to save you time). They will be named as the converter name (energy, power, etc).
* **roundingNum**: This cookie stores the number of digits you have chosen to round to, to auto-select the appropriate option when you next visit.

On some calculators we have included an option to remember the information you enter into the calculator, so that you don't have to type it in every time you visit. If you select this option (which is off by default), information is stored in a cookie in the browser on your device - we do not store this information ourselves.

* * *

Ezoic
-----

The Calculator Site uses a third party technology called Ezoic. Ezoic is committed to protecting your privacy and only uses the information collected lawfully in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/)

[The](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/) [privacy policy for Ezoic can be found here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/thecalculatorsite.com). The page also contains a full list of cookies used on this website.

Should you wish to, you can [change your privacy consent settings here](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/?ez_force_cookie_consent=1).

* * *

Third Party Advertising
-----------------------

We use Ezoic, Google, Media.net and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Your continued use of this web site confirms your acceptance of this.

We and third-party vendors may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as Google advertising cookies) or other third-party identifiers together.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, please [see the privacy policy at Google.com.](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

* * *

Third Party Cookies
-------------------

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" in your browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the The Calculator Site website. Google uses a cookie to enable it to serve ads to the user based on the user's visit to the The Calculator Site website and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI's consumer opt-out). Should you wish to opt out directly as a web user, Google Analytics' has available opt-outs for the web [available here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

More information on how to opt out of the use of the these cookies can be found in [Google's ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

* * *

Calculator and converter forms on this website
----------------------------------------------

Individual information you enter into the converter and calculator forms on this website is not stored. Results are simply calculated and returned to you on the screen based upon the data you have entered. The only exceptions to this are the productivity cookies mentioned at the top of this page.

* * *

Changes to this privacy policy
------------------------------

We reserve the right to change and update this privacy policy whenever we wish. Please revisit and review this page regularly for any updates.

Popular features

1. [How Much is a TRILLION?](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/articles/finance/how-much-is-a-trillion.php)
2. [How Long Does it Take to Walk a Mile?](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/health/how-long-to-walk-a-mile)
3. [How Many Miles is 10,000 Steps?](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/articles/health/10000-steps-in-miles.php)
4. [How to Calculate Square Footage](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/articles/units/how-to-calculate-square-footage.php)
5. [How Long Will it Take to Save?](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/finance/calculators/how-long-to-save)
6. [The Compound Interest Formula](https://www.thecalculatorsite.com/finance/calculators/compound-interest-formula)

Calculate percentage additions and deductions with our handy calculator.

* * *

Discover the number one song and movie on the day you were born.

#### Finance

#### Home & Garden

#### Cooking

#### Company

[](https://www.facebook.com/thecalculatorsite "Visit our Facebook page")© Copyright 2024, Hazell Industries Hazell Industries Ltd, 124 City Road, London. EC1V 2NX
